<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-25T15:33:45+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><subtitle>Build Jekyll site with the GitBook style.
</subtitle><author><name>Mammoth</name></author><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.04</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-25-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.04" /><published>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-25-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="third-party-connector-postgresqlmssql---allow-selection-of-tables-from-different-schemas">Third party connector PostgreSQL,MSSQL - Allow selection of tables from different schemas</h4>
<p>Mammoth now enables the selection of tables with their corresponding schema under the database. It presents a list of available schemas and then lists the tables under each schema, making it easier to navigate and access the desired tables.</p>

<h4 id="improved-positoning-of-data-library-line-items">Improved positoning of data library line items</h4>
<p>Mammoth has made significant improvements to its landing page, including the addition of an informative “Info” section for datasets and a more organized layout for line items.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>We have resolved the issue with the random refresh on Dataview pages.</li>
  <li>The editing of the lookup rule is displaying an error regarding an invalid column name.</li>
  <li>The simultaneous addition of multiple files has caused the dataset to become stuck in a processing state.</li>
  <li>In a specific scenario, the Branchout/Crosstab tasks were not appearing within the pipeline.</li>
  <li>When new batch will come in and dataset auto sync is off,The new batch goes in sync pending state.</li>
  <li>Webhook creation feature was missing from home page.</li>
  <li>Lookup task description was not showing up in the pipeline.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.01</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-02-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.01" /><published>2023-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-02-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>The column browser should stay disabled when the pipeline has an error. This has been fixed now.</li>
  <li>Added tooltip messages for disabled items when the pipeline is in error.</li>
  <li>Added an error message when the user tries to delete a View which has been used in a join rule elsewhere.</li>
  <li>When the column name is long, the data type is not visible in the Report. This has been fixed.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.52</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-29-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.52" /><published>2022-12-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-29-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fix">Defect fix</h3>

<ul>
  <li>In some scenarios,the export task would not run by itself on data updates.This has been fixed now.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fix]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.51</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-22-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.51" /><published>2022-12-22T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-22-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="mammoth-now-supports-duplicating-views-when-duplicating-datasets">Mammoth now supports duplicating Views when duplicating Datasets.</h4>
<p>When a user duplicates a data source,now they can choose to duplicate the data itself as well as any views and pipelines associated with the data source. This can save time and effort by allowing users to quickly create copies of existing data sources and their associated views and pipelines.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Clicking on the Mammoth icon opened the root folder in the Data Library. Now the Dataset name is clickable and opens the folder in  which the Dataset exists. Clicking on the Mammoth icon continues to open the root folder.</li>
  <li>Reset the view throws incorrect notification.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.50</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-13-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.50" /><published>2022-12-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-13-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="show-original-column-names">Show original column names.</h4>
<p>If a column is renamed in a View, it is difficult to find the original name. Mammoth now shows the original name in the column header on hover.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Apply Filter - Second column name does not appear in function panel and task description.</li>
  <li>Navbar is not fixed in settings page.It moves on scroll.</li>
  <li>Publish to DB - Continuous loader on rerun .</li>
  <li>Batch column section in preview panel- Cancel button overlaps the text.</li>
  <li>File upload modal- Close icon shows incorrect tooltip message.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="api-modifications">API modifications</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Modification request tracker mechanism has been removed and the functionality for this has moved to future request service.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.49</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-07-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.49" /><published>2022-12-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-07-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="provide-support-for-appendreplace-options-in-sftp-pulls-based-on-date-patterns-in-file-names">Provide support for append/replace options in SFTP pulls based on date patterns in file names.</h4>
<p>Mammoth now supports option to append or replace data in SFTP connector with one
time or periodic data pulls. If period option is chosen and the User provides a
date pattern on file names, the latest file matching date pattern is picked for
append or replace into the Dataset at the end of every period.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>When a file type dataset was added with new batch the dataset source type
became to append type.</li>
  <li>Explore Card Summary Average shows incorrect value in some scenarios.</li>
  <li>Selecting columns in the grid does not select the columns in column browser.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="beta-features">Beta features</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Bulk replace rule in Mammoth has supported fuzzy search for long. With this
enhancement the User can now control the fuzziness threshold themselves.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.47</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-11-24-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.47" /><published>2022-11-24T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-24T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-11-24-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="support-for-join-with-different-column-types">Support for join with different column types.</h4>
<p>Mammoth now allows for doing join even if data types are different. This is now
supported for joining text with numeric columns and vice versa. When such a join
is done, Mammoth internally casts the joined key column to the expected type.</p>

<h4 id="support-for-single-sign-on">Support for Single sign on</h4>
<p>Mammoth now support its customers to sign in with Google besides email and password based authentication.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Rectified a few issues when ordering tasks in pipeline</li>
  <li>Updated mails to match the revised brand</li>
  <li>Join rule drop down does not show the Views with the join rule is pipeline is
in auto run off mode</li>
  <li>The join rule drop-down was not showing the views to select from when the join rule is new in the pipeline and auto-run off.</li>
  <li>Pipeline reorder - Cancelling reorder was not reinstating the reordered step.</li>
  <li>Pipeline - Discarding changes was not updating steps position in UI.</li>
  <li>Failure to fix Export - PostgreSQL not acknowledged. It was failing silently.</li>
  <li>Reports were not showing proper date formats.</li>
  <li>Index row size was exceeding max value: Postgres error in backend and because of this error branchout to ds was failing.</li>
  <li>Account list didn’t have a vertical scroll bar to navigate when the user is part of multiple accounts.</li>
  <li>Pasting crosstab task was showing incorrect name i.e branchout in the pipeline.</li>
  <li>Branch out - Dataset name was not showing up when opened to edit the action in auto-run off mode.</li>
  <li>After OAuth type identity creation, Mammoth navigates to the file uploads tab instead of respective integration.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>karthick</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.46</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-11-17-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.46" /><published>2022-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-11-17T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-11-17-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="support-for-custom-domains-for-salesforce-integration">Support for custom domains for Salesforce integration.</h4>
<p>Mammoth now supports salesforce sign-in for custom domains besides the main salesforce domain.</p>

<h4 id="third-party-connectors-in-mammoth-now-allow-for-replacing-data-in-the-dataset-with-new-rows-of-data-in-the-remote-data-store">Third-party connectors in Mammoth now allow for replacing data in the dataset with new rows of data in the remote data store.</h4>
<p>If you have a table in your database to which rows are added periodically and you want to process only the latest rows in Mammoth, you can do this now. Earlier you could pull the latest rows in Mammoth but you would keep all in Mammoth (using the Combine mode in data pulls). Now, Mammoth allows you to pull the latest batch of data in the remote table in replace mode.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>In some scenarios Pipeline in a View would show loader thus preventing access to the task Menu. This is now resolved.</li>
  <li>Error column shows up in column selection field of the task after copy pasting a task.</li>
  <li>Canceling a function shows inocorrect data types in a specific scenario.</li>
  <li>Format not handled correctly for numeric columns.</li>
  <li>Multiple issues in Search bar on account landing.</li>
  <li>A file with unambigous date column asks for user input.</li>
  <li>Pending update summary doesn’t show right details.</li>
  <li>A file is showing empty grid.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry></feed>