<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-23T16:30:39+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><subtitle>Build Jekyll site with the GitBook style.
</subtitle><author><name>Mammoth</name></author><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.12</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-23-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.12" /><published>2023-03-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-23-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Addressed an issue with the window function not working correctly when used with a date column, resulting in the same column being produced.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where creating a new branchout and sending data from multiple views resulted in duplicate datasets being created.</li>
  <li>Third-party connector modal - Fixed an issue where Zoom OAuth redirection gave an error when the browser was already logged in for Zoom.</li>
  <li>Addressed an issue where folder deletion was showing a loader.</li>
  <li>Fixed an error that was appearing in the console due to a Join rule.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where an error icon was shown while creating the BigQuery export action.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.10</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-11-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.10" /><published>2023-03-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-11-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="smart-combine-on-big-query-is-now-available-as-an-alpha-feature-on-request">Smart combine on Big Query is now available as an alpha feature (on request)</h4>
<ul>
  <li>Now, users can remove and edit a BigQuery service file in the export section. Also, multiple service files can be added.</li>
  <li>Introduced a feature called Smart combine. This allows users to merge new data into an existing exported table. If the same set of key columns is reported, the corresponding values are updated. If a new set of key columns come in, they are now added to the table. Supported on Big Query.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue where the BigQuery table name was not displayed in error notifications.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue in the dropdown for the Unique sequence column in the Connectors modal where the names of the column in the list were missing column type suffixes.</li>
  <li>Resolved a problem where SFTP took too long to list files.</li>
  <li>Addresses an issue in the Edit Query Modal that prevented it from opening or displaying older datasets without continuous loading.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.09</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-01-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.09" /><published>2023-03-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-01-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="mammoth-now-warns-if-there-are-duplicate-values-in-the-joined-key-column-in-the-join-rule">Mammoth now warns if there are duplicate values in the joined key column in the Join rule</h4>
<p>Mammoth now warns if there are non-unique values in the key column of the joined View. This is useful when the raw data or blended data is expected to have unique values but due to some flaws in the process, there are duplicated keys resulting in erroneous end results. This warning would help catch such issues early.</p>

<h4 id="back-button-for-data-addition-modals">Back Button for Data Addition Modals</h4>
<p>Data addition modals now have a back button that redirects to the main menu.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Addressed the issue where pipeline rules were being modified unexpectedly when changing the foreign view in join.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where window function sort was becoming undefined upon duplicating the view.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue of column names not being generated correctly when changing data settings for CSV files in the file processor.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where Apply template was not working on views.</li>
  <li>Connectors Modal: Fixed the issue of Text type columns being listed in the unique sequence column dropdown.</li>
  <li>Connectors Modal: Schedule option was erroneously showing up for connectors where this is not applicable. This has been fixed.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where user with no account would see a loader after sign in.</li>
  <li>When a Branch Out Task is suspended or deleted, Mammoth deletes the contributed batch in the branched-out Dataset. This is also the behaviour now when a View containing such a Branch Out task is deleted or reset.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.08</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-21-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.08" /><published>2023-02-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-21-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="mongodb-connector">MongoDB Connector</h4>
<p>Mammoth now includes the MongoDB connector using the cdata driver version 22.0.8389.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>The folder breadcrumbs have been reorganized to improve navigation.</li>
  <li>The column browser selection previously experienced scrolling lag and selection issues. These issues have been resolved.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue with third party connectors where it was possible for users to create an existing identity multiple times while editing another connection.</li>
  <li>The issue where deleting a View in a Dataset with multiple Views caused another View to disappear has been fixed.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.07</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-13-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.07" /><published>2023-02-13T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-13T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-13-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="support-for-stored-procedures-in-salesforce">Support for Stored Procedures in Salesforce</h4>
<p>Users can now execute stored procedure queries in the query box.</p>

<h4 id="improved-messages-in-add-data-modal">Improved messages in Add Data modal.</h4>
<p>Mammoth has enhanced the messaging for the components like My computer, Webhooks, etc under Add Data modal.</p>

<h4 id="enhanced-explore-card-performance">Enhanced Explore card performance</h4>
<p>Mammoth has significantly improved its performance when opening multiple Explore Cards.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Resolved an error that was appearing in the console due to a Join rule.</li>
  <li>Added a message to display when there are duplicate column names in the query result for Postgres and Redshift.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where the warning modal was not appearing after editing a query for an existing dataset for third-party connectors.</li>
  <li>Resolved UI issues in the Third-Party Connector for Data Addition.</li>
  <li>Stabilized the movement of the navigation bar when scrolling up or down.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.06</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-06-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.06" /><published>2023-02-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-02-06-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="new-data-addition-modal">New Data addition modal</h4>
<p>Migrated existing APIs &amp; Databases tab to Vue for improved UI for adding data through File, Webhook, URL, and Third-Party connectors.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Fixed Sharepoint dataset creation and loader display issue.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where renaming a View would show error motifs for a legitimate case.</li>
  <li>Fixed the missing progress modal when changes are applied in draft mode.</li>
  <li>Fixed an alignment issue in Branchout to dataset.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.04</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-25-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.04" /><published>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-25T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-25-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="third-party-connector-postgresql-mssql---allow-selection-of-tables-from-different-schemas">Third-party connector PostgreSQL, MSSQL - Allow selection of tables from different schemas</h4>
<p>Mammoth now enables the selection of tables with their corresponding schema under the database. It presents a list of available schemas and then lists the tables under each schema, making it easier to navigate and access the desired tables.</p>

<h4 id="improved-positioning-of-data-library-line-items">Improved positioning of data library line items</h4>
<p>Mammoth has made significant improvements to its landing page, including the addition of an informative “Info” section for datasets and a more organized layout for line items.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>We have resolved the issue with the random refresh on the Dataview pages.</li>
  <li>The editing of the lookup rule is displaying an error regarding an invalid column name.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where the Dataset appears frozen on the addition of multiple files.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where Branchout or Crosstab tasks won’t appear in the Pipeline.</li>
  <li>When a new batch will come in and dataset auto sync is off, The new batch goes into sync pending state.</li>
  <li>Webhook creation feature was missing from the home page.</li>
  <li>Lookup task description was not showing up in the pipeline.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.01</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-02-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.01" /><published>2023-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-02T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-01-02-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>The column browser should stay disabled when the pipeline has an error. This has been fixed now.</li>
  <li>Added tooltip messages for disabled items when the pipeline is in error.</li>
  <li>Added an error message when the user tries to delete a View which has been used in a join rule elsewhere.</li>
  <li>When the column name is long, the data type is not visible in the Report. This has been fixed.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.52</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-29-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.52" /><published>2022-12-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-29-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fix">Defect fix</h3>

<ul>
  <li>In some scenarios,the export task would not run by itself on data updates.This has been fixed now.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fix]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2022.51</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-22-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2022.51" /><published>2022-12-22T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-22T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022-12-22-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="mammoth-now-supports-duplicating-views-when-duplicating-datasets">Mammoth now supports duplicating Views when duplicating Datasets.</h4>
<p>When a user duplicates a data source,now they can choose to duplicate the data itself as well as any views and pipelines associated with the data source. This can save time and effort by allowing users to quickly create copies of existing data sources and their associated views and pipelines.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Clicking on the Mammoth icon opened the root folder in the Data Library. Now the Dataset name is clickable and opens the folder in  which the Dataset exists. Clicking on the Mammoth icon continues to open the root folder.</li>
  <li>Reset the view throws incorrect notification.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry></feed>