<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-08-14T12:57:24+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><subtitle>Build Jekyll site with the GitBook style.
</subtitle><author><name>Mammoth</name></author><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.32</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-08-11-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.32" /><published>2023-08-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-08-11-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements:</h3>

<h4 id="sftp-access-enhancement">SFTP Access Enhancement:</h4>
<p>You can now access SFTP through an SSH key for third-party imports. In addition to password-based authentication, this update introduces authentication using a private SSH key.</p>

<h4 id="streamlined-column-copying-alpha-feature">Streamlined Column Copying (Alpha Feature):</h4>
<p>Copying multiple columns is now more efficient. Instead of creating a separate rule per column, users can use a single copy rule for multiple columns. This functionality is accessible through the transform menu and enhances workflow efficiency.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect Fixes:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Resolved an inconsistency in Branch out rule when deleting the resultant dataset.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where pipeline changes were not being reflected in the data flow status modal.</li>
  <li>Resolved the “Publish to DB” error that occurred.</li>
  <li>Fixed the continuous loader problem during the application of copy column rule through pasting.</li>
  <li>Third-Party Connector: Resolved the Salesforce error that was occurring when attempting to create a dataset.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where performing consecutive actions like adding, deleting, or suspending batches did not maintain the correct row count in all views</li>
  <li>Fixed the third-party OAuth connector identity creation redirection issue.</li>
  <li>Resolved the problem of copy-pasting tasks not functioning correctly for certain tasks, which was causing a loader to appear.</li>
  <li>Corrected the task card’s display of incorrect row count for Window function tasks when “Limit ranking” was selected.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements:]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.30</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-07-26-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.30" /><published>2023-07-26T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-07-26T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-07-26-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements:</h3>
<h4 id="password-protected-xlsx-file-support">Password Protected XLSX File Support:</h4>
<p>Users can now open password-protected XLSX files directly from file uploads or through SFTP connections. This enhancement enables secure handling of sensitive data.</p>

<h4 id="maximizable-filter-condition-popover">Maximizable Filter Condition Popover:</h4>
<p>We have improved the filter condition popover by allowing users to maximize it to its full size.Now, users can easily work with complex filter conditions.</p>

<h4 id="optimized-explore-cards-and-filter-widget">Optimized Explore Cards and Filter Widget:</h4>
<p>We have optimized the explore cards and filter widget functionality. When users select multiple granular values in a numeric column, the filter will now consolidate them into a single condition instead of creating numerous separate conditions.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect Fixes:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue where Running total and Rank functions didn’t automatically select the column when chosen from the column menu.</li>
  <li>Fixed the problem of the “Clear” button text going out of the field in Edit Query modal.</li>
  <li>Resolved the conflict arising from having the same connector keys for data import and export for third-party connectors.</li>
  <li>Fixed the bug where the grid was showing the wrong column order.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue causing MSSQL export validation to fail during editing.</li>
  <li>Resolved the problem with Join rule’s data sync status not properly retaining its status when the join rule is restored.</li>
  <li>Fixed the error where applying a filter on an explore card was not showing the result, and the loader was seen on the row count summary.</li>
  <li>Fixed the browser crash occurring due to datagrid refreshes when applying a template containing 125 tasks on a dataset containing 55 columns.</li>
  <li>Resolved the data sync issue by now deleting the dependencies when an action is suspended.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements: Password Protected XLSX File Support: Users can now open password-protected XLSX files directly from file uploads or through SFTP connections. This enhancement enables secure handling of sensitive data.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.27</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-07-06-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.27" /><published>2023-07-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-07-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-07-06-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements:</h3>
<h4 id="data-sync-controls">Data Sync Controls:</h4>
<p>Data Sync now provides enhanced capabilities for managing data connections and controlling the flow of data between different components. With these improvements, you can:</p>
<h6 id="apreview-panel">a)Preview Panel:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Gain access to data sync controls.</li>
  <li>Access a wider range of dataset properties and view information.</li>
  <li>Access view controls directly from preview panel.</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="bpipeline">b)Pipeline:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Exercise more control over data handling at each step of the pipeline.</li>
  <li>Utilize the new data-sync toggle option to manage data synchronization.</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="improved-data-flow-status">Improved Data Flow Status:</h4>
<p>The workflow status modal has been enhanced to offer a comprehensive overview of active pipelines and data flows. Key features of this update include:</p>

<h6 id="a-action-required">a) Action Required:</h6>

<ul>
  <li>Pending Data Updates: If an ongoing data flow encounters a task or view with data sync turned off, preventing further progress, the task and view details will be displayed in this section.</li>
  <li>Pending Pipeline Changes: Any pipelines in draft mode that have pending changes will be highlighted here.</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="b-active-pipelines">b) Active Pipelines:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Running: Providing information on currently running pipelines.</li>
  <li>Queued: Displaying information on pipelines in the queue.</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="crun-updates-from-workflow-status-modal">c)Run updates from workflow status modal:</h6>
<p>Now, in addition to viewing pending data updates and pipeline changes, you can directly initiate the execution of these updates from within the workflow status modal itself.</p>

<h4 id="show-exports-in-data-out-links-">Show exports in Data-Out Links :</h4>
<p>The data out indicator in the data library has been enhanced to display various exports, such as SQL Server, Postgres, and more, alongside other data connections.</p>

<h4 id="allow-downloading-csv-at-step-level-">Allow downloading CSV at step level :</h4>
<p>Mammoth now offers the capability to download CSV files directly from the preview data at different steps within the pipeline, providing greater flexibility and convenience for data analysis and manipulation.</p>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect Fixes:</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue where opening multiple views in a dataset sequentially would cause the page to become laggy and unresponsive over time.</li>
  <li>Fixed the problem causing significant delay and page hang when opening the branchout function panel with a large number of columns.</li>
  <li>Third Party Modal : Addressed the issue causing the query box to fluctuate inconsistently during the “Retrieve Latest Data” operation.</li>
  <li>Improved overall performance for larger pipelines, resulting in better performance even with larger datasets.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements: Data Sync Controls: Data Sync now provides enhanced capabilities for managing data connections and controlling the flow of data between different components. With these improvements, you can: a)Preview Panel: Gain access to data sync controls. Access a wider range of dataset properties and view information. Access view controls directly from preview panel.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.26</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-06-27-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.26" /><published>2023-06-27T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-27T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-06-27-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Resolved the issue where the “Move to” UI in the Folder feature had additional space.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where not all assets of a workspace were transferred to the target user.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue of element overflowing the viewport on &lt;Data Library?&gt;.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where downloading as CSV would result in downloading the CSV file twice.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where reset on the foreign view in the Join rule did not update the dependent data sources.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where Branch out did not exit the error state when columns were reordered and all columns were correctly mapped.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where the Pipeline remained in an error state even after fixing the rule.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where creating a data source in combine mode and a unique sequence column failed for Snowflake integration.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where email notifications were not sent when branch out or join operations encountered errors.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where the Duplicate entry modal in the Join rule displayed overlapping text when the key column had duplicate values and they were long strings.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where incorrect data was displayed in the Third-party connector modal when quickly changing the table name.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where applying a template or adding a group aggregate rule would result in an empty grid.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where the “Download as CSV” feature did not export only the filtered data when explore card filters were applied.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue in “Date difference” rule to ensure that the result of the date difference is always a positive integer when the start date is earlier than the end date.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.24</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-06-14-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.24" /><published>2023-06-14T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-06-14T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-06-14-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h3 id="action-bar-and-data-grid-redesign">Action Bar and Data Grid Redesign</h3>

<p>Mammoth has introduced a fresh new design for the action bar and data grid, aiming to provide an enhanced user experience through improved interfaces. In this update, you will notice significant changes in the top portion called the action bar and the grid where data is displayed.</p>
<h5 id="ui-changes">UI Changes:</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Streamlined Transform Menu: The Transform menu has been updated to provide a more intuitive and user-friendly experience.</li>
  <li>Enhanced Column Browser: The column browser has undergone improvements to offer a better browsing experience.</li>
  <li>Relocated Features: The option to publish reports, publish databases, and access the CSV link has been moved to more accessible locations within the new UI, ensuring easier usage and navigation.</li>
</ul>

<p>Please note that while the overall functionality remains the same, various features have been repositioned within the new UI to provide a more streamlined and efficient workflow</p>
<h5 id="removed-feature">Removed Feature:</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Quick Export Option: The Quick Export option, previously located in the top right corner, has been removed from the UI.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>The issue causing race condition has been resolved, ensuring that no stale data appears in the explore card.</li>
  <li>The problem of infinite scrolling in grid data has been fixed.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.21</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-05-23-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.21" /><published>2023-05-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-05-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-05-23-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Edit query - Fixed the issue where the datapull fails in case of a unique sequence column during query editing.</li>
  <li>Edit query- Resolved the problem where the unique sequence column name was not appearing in the ‘On refresh’ section of the Preview.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where the option to add data was not visible when there were only reports available in account landing page.</li>
  <li>Third party connetor modal- Resolved the inability to create a Hubspot identity.</li>
  <li>Fixed the issue where BigQuery was not displaying the correct error message when encountering an error.</li>
  <li>Resolved the intermittent problem where the Branch out logo was not showing up for line items on the landing page.</li>
  <li>Resolved the issue where moving a DS/Folder to the Data Library was not possible.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="api-modifications">API modifications</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Fixed the issue where the API rate limit on post/patch requests was not appropriately configured, resulting in slow loading of explore cards when a user had multiple cards on multiple views and opened them simultaneously. The limit has now been resolved and set to 60.</li>
  <li>Added middleware for FastAPI setup to include authentication checks in the setup.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.17</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-04-29-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.17" /><published>2023-04-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-04-29-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="email-notification-for-pipeline-errors">Email notification for Pipeline errors</h4>
<ul>
  <li>Mammoth now provides email alerts to users when a task fails during pipeline execution</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Fixed an issue where zip file uploads were not working.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where users were unable to move a DS/Folder to the Data Library.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where column rename in foreign view did not reflect in the current view.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue with the missing update for in/out links for deleted View.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where dragging a file directly from the browser to the data library did not work every time.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue for missing display of internal export task errors.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="security-patches">Security Patches</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Moved our a few values stored in browser local storage</li>
  <li>Implemented rate limiting on APIs to prevent request bombardment</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.15</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-04-11-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.15" /><published>2023-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-04-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-04-11-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>
<h4 id="improved-regex-error-handling-an-alpha-feature-on-request">Improved Regex Error Handling (An alpha feature on request)</h4>
<ul>
  <li>Mammoth improved the handling of regex errors in the Extract Text rule by implementing a validator to disallow invalid regex, such as ], [A-Z{1,3}. Spaces to be matched now have to be explicitly mentioned with a preceeding backslash. <space> changes to <backslash><space></space></backslash></space></li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue where data export to Redshift was not working.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where copy-pasting the branch out did not work correctly.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where the underline for Add sort had not been removed in the Top bottom rule and Window function rule.</li>
  <li>Fixed UI and functional issues around identities, queries, and table names in the Third Party Connector Modal.</li>
  <li>Third Party Connector Modal: Resolved an issue where  Postgresql did not display the correct dataset after datapull.</li>
  <li>Third Party Connector Modal: Resolved an issue where MySql merged the next row data with the previous row when the previous row data ended with a single backslash (“").</li>
  <li>An issue has been resolved where renamed column names did not appear in the task pipeline for the Join rule.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where the exported pipeline in Branchout to ds was re-running even after a manual data push.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where duplicating views with Dataset wasn’t working as expected</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements Improved Regex Error Handling (An alpha feature on request) Mammoth improved the handling of regex errors in the Extract Text rule by implementing a validator to disallow invalid regex, such as ], [A-Z{1,3}. Spaces to be matched now have to be explicitly mentioned with a preceeding backslash. changes to]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.13</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-28-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.13" /><published>2023-03-28T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-28T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-28-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Addressed an issue with the window function not working correctly when used with a date column, resulting in the same column being produced.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where creating a new branchout and sending data from multiple views resulted in duplicate datasets being created.</li>
  <li>Third-party connector modal - Fixed an issue where Zoom OAuth redirection gave an error when the browser was already logged in for Zoom.</li>
  <li>Addressed an issue where folder deletion was showing a loader.</li>
  <li>Fixed an error that was appearing in the console due to a Join rule.</li>
  <li>Resolved an issue where an error icon was shown while creating the BigQuery export action.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue where ‘Get Started’ link was showing an empty page.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defect fixes]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Release 2023.10</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-11-release.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Release 2023.10" /><published>2023-03-11T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-11T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/release</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023-03-11-release.html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="enhancements">Enhancements</h3>

<h4 id="smart-combine-on-big-query-is-now-available-as-an-alpha-feature-on-request">Smart combine on Big Query is now available as an alpha feature (on request)</h4>
<ul>
  <li>Now, users can remove and edit a BigQuery service file in the export section. Also, multiple service files can be added.</li>
  <li>Introduced a feature called Smart combine. This allows users to merge new data into an existing exported table. If the same set of key columns is reported, the corresponding values are updated. If a new set of key columns come in, they are now added to the table. Supported on Big Query.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="defect-fixes">Defect fixes</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Resolved an issue where the BigQuery table name was not displayed in error notifications.</li>
  <li>Fixed an issue in the dropdown for the Unique sequence column in the Connectors modal where the names of the column in the list were missing column type suffixes.</li>
  <li>Resolved a problem where SFTP took too long to list files.</li>
  <li>Addresses an issue in the Edit Query Modal that prevented it from opening or displaying older datasets without continuous loading.</li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>Priya</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancements]]></summary></entry></feed>